A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Press Materials FA1322
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Record Group 1, Accessions 2017:062 and 2017:078, 1951-2002; 1; 32.713 Cubic Feet 29 LTR size, 1 Half-LTR size, 44 LGL size, and 2 Half-LGL size Hollinger boxes and 1 oversize document box
  - Press releases, 1951-1975, 1990-1993; 1; 9.545 Cubic Feet About 1 half LGL size Hollinger box, 2 full LGL size Hollinger boxes, and 22 LTR size Hollinger boxes
    - News from the Ford Foundation releases, No. 1-295, 1951-1962; 1; 3.19 Cubic Feet About 1 Half LGL sized Hollinger box and 7.75 LTR sized Hollinger boxes
      - 279. Fellowships in business administration and economics, 1962 June 12 (Box 9, Folder 290)
      - 280. Legal education in Africa, 1962 June 20 (Box 9, Folder 291)
      - 281. Grants to concert artists, 1962 June 26 (Box 9, Folder 292)
      - 282. Special Program in Education - Private liberal-arts colleges, 1962 June 27 (Box 9, Folder 293)
      - 283. Announcement of 1960s' Ford Foundation program areas, 1962 July 1 (Box 9, Folder 294)
      - 284. Educational television (ETV) - Nationally and in New York, 1962 July 5 (Box 9, Folder 295)
      - 285. Reorganization of the American Council on Education, 1962 July 19 (Box 9, Folder 296)
      - 286. Fellowships for administrative internships in the performing arts and No. 285 copy, 1962 July (Box 9, Folder 297)
      - 287. Research and training resources on Latin America, 1962 August 1 (Box 9, Folder 298)
      - 288. Background Facts - Finances of the Ford Foundation, 1962 September 14 (Box 9, Folder 299)
      - 289. Grant to Baltimore City Board of Education, 1962 October 4 (Box 9, Folder 300)
      - 290. Grants to theater companies, 1962 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 301)
      - 290a. Attachment 1 to No. 290, 1962 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 302)
      - 290b. Attachment 2 to No. 290, 1962 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 303)
      - 291. Ford Foundation President Henry T. Heald address at Princeton University, 1962 October 13 (Box 9, Folder 304)
      - 292. Grant to Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1962 October 30 (Box 9, Folder 305)
      - 292a. Grant to the University of Brazil in Rio de Janeiro, 1962 October 30 (Box 9, Folder 306)
      - 293. Plan to scale down business education program, 1962 November 25 (Box 9, Folder 307)
      - 294. Special Program in Education - Grants to universities, 1962 December 17 (Box 9, Folder 308)
      - 295. International studies in undergraduate education, 1962 December 20 (Box 9, Folder 309)
    - News from the Ford Foundation releases No. 370-771, 1964-1970; 2; 3.61 Cubic Feet About 9.5 LTR size Hollinger boxes
      Subseries contains News from the Ford Foundation press releases No. 370-771. Press releases in this subseries provide evidence of the Ford Foundation's expanded efforts to assist minority communities in the late 1960s.
      The subseries originally contained a significant gap in its holdings. When Record Group 1, Accessions 2017:062 and 2017:078 were processed in February 2018, the subseries did not include News from the Ford Foundation press releases No. 676-735 (July 1969 – July 1970). These press releases were later discovered in Record Group 2, Accession 2018:088. The decision was made during the processing of Record Group 2 to move the documents into Record Group 1 in order so that the relationship between the press releases could be better represented.
      - 370. History of grants in the State of Iowa booklet, 1964 May (Box 9, Folder 310)
      - 371. History of grants in the State of Nebraska booklet, 1964 May (Box 9, Folder 311)
      - 372. History of grants in the State of Maine booklet, 1964 May (Box 9, Folder 312)
      - 372. History of grants in the State of Rhode Island booklet, 1964 June (Box 9, Folder 313)
      - 373. Results of several fellowship programs, 1964 May 10 (Box 9, Folder 314)
      - 374. Finances of the Ford Foundation, 1964 May 20 (Box 9, Folder 315)
      - 375. Science and Engineering Program - Forgivable loans, 1964 June 10 (Box 9, Folder 316)
      - 376. History of grants in the State of Connecticut booklet, 1964 June (Box 9, Folder 317)
      - 377. W. McNeil Lowry appointment, 1964 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 318)
      - 378. Education in Alaska, 1964 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 319)
      - 379. Grants to Negro colleges and the Atlanta University Center, 1964 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 320)
      - 380. Fact sheet for No. 379, 1964 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 321)
      - 381. Police administration grants, 1964 July 2 (Box 9, Folder 322)
      - 382. History of grants in the State of Wisconsin booklet, 1964 July (Box 9, Folder 323)
      - 383. National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1964 July 12 (Box 9, Folder 324)
      - 384. History of grants in the State of Colorado booklet, 1964 July (Box 9, Folder 325)
      - 385. Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA) - Awards to faculty and graduate students, 1964 July 16 (Box 9, Folder 326)
      - 386. Education Program - State University of Iowa and Ontario Curriculum Institute, 1964 July 24 (Box 10, Folder 327)
      - 387. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Administrative internships, 1964 August 3 (Box 10, Folder 328)
      - 388. International Division - East-West exchanges, 1964 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 329)
      - 389. International Training and Research Program (ITR) - Postdoctoral fellows for Latin America, 1964 August 13 (Box 10, Folder 330)
      - 390. Malcolm C. Moos appointment, 1964 August 19 (Box 10, Folder 331)
      - 391. Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA), 1964 August 21 (Box 10, Folder 332)
      - 392. History of grants in the State of Massachusetts booklet, 1964 September (Box 10, Folder 333)
      - 393. History of grants in the Southwest States booklet and No. 392 copy, 1964 September (Box 10, Folder 334)
      - 394. History of grants in the State of Kansas booklet, 1964 September (Box 10, Folder 335)
      - 395. Verne S. Atwater and Thomas H. Lenagh appointments, 1964 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 336)
      - 396. Ford Foundation new building, 1964 September 29 (Box 10, Folder 337)
        File includes a statement from Kevin Roche, one of the architects responsible for designing the Ford Foundation New York City headquarters building.
      - 397. Theater, 1964 October 2 (Box 10, Folder 338)
      - 398. Vocational education and Public Affairs Program (PA), 1964 October 8 (Box 10, Folder 339)
      - 399. History of grants in the State of Oklahoma booklet, 1964 October (Box 10, Folder 340)
      - 400. International Division - Technical University of Berlin, 1964 October 13 (Box 10, Folder 341)
      - 401. Science and Engineering Program and the National Historical Publications Commission, 1964 October 20 (Box 10, Folder 342)
      - 402. History of grants in the State of Missouri booklet, 1964 October (Box 10, Folder 343)
      - 403. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Juvenile courts, 1964 October 28 (Box 10, Folder 344)
      - 404. Overseas Development Program (OD) - Agriculture, 1964 November 15 (Box 10, Folder 345)
      - 405. Copy of No. 404, 1964 November 15 (Box 10, Folder 346)
      - 406. Independent study programs, 1964 December 3 (Box 10, Folder 347)
      - 407. Special Program - Universities, 1964 December 17 (Box 10, Folder 348)
      - 407a. Announcement of William K. Shaughnessy death, 1964 December 21 (Box 10, Folder 349)
      - 408. Negro business education, 1964 December 22 (Box 10, Folder 350)
      - 409. Translation center at the University of Texas, 1964 December 30 (Box 10, Folder 351)
      - 410. 1964 Annual Report, 1965 January 3 (Box 10, Folder 352)
      - 411. International Training and Research Program (ITR), 1965 January 10 (Box 10, Folder 353)
      - 412. First alternate lead for No. 411, 1965 January 10 (Box 10, Folder 354)
      - 413. Second alternate lead for No. 411, 1965 January 10 (Box 10, Folder 355)
      - 414. School improvement program, 1965 January 18 (Box 10, Folder 356)
      - 415. Disposition of Ford Motor Company stock, 1965 January 27 (Box 10, Folder 357)
      - 416. International Division - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1965 February 14 (Box 10, Folder 358)
      - 417. British version for No. 416, 1965 February 14 (Box 10, Folder 359)
      - 418. Population, 1965 February 24 (Box 10, Folder 360)
      - 419. History of grants in Alaska and Hawaii booklet, 1965 March (Box 10, Folder 361)
      - 420. History of grants in the District of Columbia, 1965 March (Box 10, Folder 362)
      - 421. Overseas Development Program (OD) - Rice research, 1965 March 7 (Box 10, Folder 363)
      - 422. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Awards for reporters, critics, and editors, 1965 March 15 (Box 10, Folder 364)
      - 423. History of grants in the State of New Jersey booklet, 1965 March (Box 10, Folder 365)
      - 424. Harry E. Wilhelm and John F. Hilliard appointments, 1965 March 28 (Box 10, Folder 366)
      - 425. History of grants in Delaware and Maryland booklet, 1965 April (Box 10, Folder 367)
      - 426. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Community programs, 1965 March 31 (Box 10, Folder 368)
      - 427. Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA) - Negro business career opportunities, 1965 April 5 (Box 10, Folder 369)
      - 428. Educationally disadvantaged children, 1965 April 12 (Box 10, Folder 370)
      - 429. Southern version of No. 428, 1965 April 12 (Box 10, Folder 371)
      - 430. Special Programs - Journalism education, 1965 April 20 (Box 10, Folder 372)
      - 431. History of grants in the State of Pennsylvania booklet, 1965 April (Box 10, Folder 373)
      - 432. National Municipal League, 1965 April 27 (Box 10, Folder 374)
      - 433. History of grants in the State of Ohio booklet, 1965 May (Box 10, Folder 375)
      - 434. School improvement - Administrators, 1965 May 2 (Box 10, Folder 376)
      - 435. History of grants in the State of North Carolina booklet, 1965 May (Box 10, Folder 377)
      - 436. History of grants in the State of South Carolina booklet, 1965 May (Box 10, Folder 378)
      - 437. International Division - Higher education in Latin America, 1965 May 13 (Box 10, Folder 379)
      - 437a. Announcement of sale of Ford Motor Company stock, 1965 May 19 (Box 10, Folder 380)
      - 438. History of grants in the State of West Virginia booklet, 1965 June (Box 10, Folder 381)
      - 439. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Museum curator fellowships, 1965 May 26 (Box 10, Folder 382)
      - 440. History of grants in the State of Arkansas booklet, 1965 June (Box 10, Folder 383)
      - 441. History of grants in the State of Virginia booklet, 1965 June (Box 10, Folder 384)
      - 442. Registration of stock sale - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), 1965 June 2 (Box 10, Folder 385)
      - 443. Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA) - Fellows, 1965 June 15 (Box 10, Folder 386)
      - 444. Law school grants, 1965 June 23 (Box 10, Folder 387)
      - 445. Bank Street College of Education, 1965 June 28 (Box 11, Folder 388)
      - 446. Alternate lead for No. 445, 1965 June 28 (Box 11, Folder 389)
      - 447. Community-supported educational television (ETV), 1965 July 13 (Box 11, Folder 390)
      - 448. Southern journalists, 1965 July 8 (Box 11, Folder 391)
      - 449. Ford Foundation President Henry T. Heald resignation, 1965 July 15 (Box 11, Folder 392)
      - 450. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Administrative interns, 1965 July 29 (Box 11, Folder 393)
      - 451. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Poverty, 1965 August 4 (Box 11, Folder 394)
      - 452. Overseas Development Program (OD) - Agriculture and population, 1965 August 12 (Box 11, Folder 395)
      - 453. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Criminal justice, 1965 August 17 (Box 11, Folder 396)
      - 454. Careers in Teaching Engineering, 1965 September 2 (Box 11, Folder 397)
      - 455. Special Program - University of Chicago, 1965 October 20 (Box 11, Folder 398)
      - 456. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Symphony orchestras, 1965 October 22 (Box 11, Folder 399)
      - 457. Grants related to state government, urban poverty, population, and other concerns, 1965 October 26 (Box 11, Folder 400)
      - 458. International Training and Research Program (ITR) - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1965 November 5 (Box 11, Folder 401)
      - 459. Copy of and alternate lead for No. 458, 1965 November 5 (Box 11, Folder 402)
      - 460. Julius S. Stratton appointment to Ford Foundation Board of Trustees Chairman, 1965 November 17 (Box 11, Folder 403)
      - 461. Population, 1965 December 1 (Box 11, Folder 404)
      - 461a. John J. McCloy confirms McGeorge Bundy to be Ford Foundation President, 1965 December 8 (Box 11, Folder 405)
      - 461b. Ford Foundation Board of Trustees formally elects McGeorge Bundy, 1965 December 10 (Box 11, Folder 406)
      - 462. Resources and Environment Program, 1965 December 16 (Box 11, Folder 407)
      - 463. Henry T. Heald establishes new firm, 1965 December 13 (Box 11, Folder 408)
      - 464. Science and technology education in developing countries, 1965 December 21 (Box 11, Folder 409)
      - 465. Some Viewpoints Concerning Agricultural Development, 1965 December 28 (Box 11, Folder 410)
      - 466. Education, 1966 January 7 (Box 11, Folder 411)
      - 467. Alternate lead for No. 466, 1966 January 7 (Box 11, Folder 412)
      - 468. Fiscal year 1965 Annual Report, 1965 December 30 (Box 11, Folder 413)
      - 468a. International studies programs and social science research related to Latin America, 1966 January 27 (Box 11, Folder 414)
      - 469. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Race relations, 1966 February 7 (Box 11, Folder 415)
      - 470. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Prison college curriculum, 1966 February 7 (Box 11, Folder 416)
      - 471. Public Affairs Program (PA) - National Council on Legal Clinics, 1966 February 7 (Box 11, Folder 417)
      - 472. John H. Loudon appointment to Ford Foundation Board of Trustees, 1966 February 14 (Box 11, Folder 418)
      - 473. International Affairs Program (IA) - Athens Agora excavation, 1966 February 18 (Box 11, Folder 419)
      - 474. Harvard-M.I.T Joint Center and scouting study, 1966 February 23 (Box 11, Folder 420)
      - 475. Alternate lead for No. 474, 1966 February 23 (Box 11, Folder 421)
      - 476. Herman Joe Holliday death, 1966 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 422)
      - 477. Education - New York City, New York and East Orange, New Jersey, 1966 March 16 (Box 11, Folder 423)
      - 478. Opportunities Industrialization Center (OIC), 1966 March 29 (Box 11, Folder 424)
      - 479. Management Council for Merit Employment, Training, and Research, 1966 March 31 (Box 11, Folder 425)
      - 480. Fred W. Friendly appointment, 1966 April 6 (Box 11, Folder 426)
      - 481. Teacher training in higher education, 1966 April 14 (Box 11, Folder 427)
      - 482. Ford Foundation President McGeorge Bundy visit to Japan, 1966 April 19 (Box 11, Folder 428)
      - 483. Engineering residencies, 1966 April 21 (Box 11, Folder 429)
      - 483a. Jewish Theological Seminary, 1966 April 22 (Box 11, Folder 430)
      - 484. Government and journalism awards, 1966 April 26 (Box 11, Folder 431)
      - 485. Alternate lead for No. 484, 1966 April 26 (Box 11, Folder 432)
      - 486. International studies in American universities, 1966 May 2 (Box 11, Folder 433)
      - 487. Housing, 1966 May 10 (Box 12, Folder 434)
      - 488. Population, 1966 May 23 (Box 12, Folder 435)
      - 488a. Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA) - Fellowships, 1966 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 436)
      - 489. Vera Institute of Justice, 1966 June 8 (Box 12, Folder 437)
      - 490. Special Program in Education, 1966 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 438)
      - 490a. Alternate version for No. 490, 1966 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 439)
      - 491. Oxford University, 1966 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 440)
      - 492. David E. Bell appointment, 1966 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 441)
      - 493. International studies, 1966 July 3 (Box 12, Folder 442)
      - 494. Symphony orchestras, 1966 July 6 (Box 12, Folder 443)
      - 495. Resources and Environment Program, 1966 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 444)
      - 496. Vocational education, 1966 July 19 (Box 12, Folder 445)
      - 496a. Critical questions raised by Medicare, 1966 July 19 (Box 12, Folder 446)
      - 497. Corrections and police training, 1966 July 25 (Box 12, Folder 447)
      - 498. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Administrative internships, 1966 July 28 (Box 12, Folder 448)
      - 499. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Ballet, 1966 August 1 (Box 12, Folder 449)
      - 500. Communication satellite, 1966 August 1 (Box 12, Folder 450)
      - 501. Population, 1966 August 16 (Box 12, Folder 451)
      - 502. Poverty Programs, 1966 August 22 (Box 12, Folder 452)
      - 503. Computerized gaming, 1966 August 28 (Box 12, Folder 453)
      - 503a.Special Program for Journalism, 1966 September (Box 12, Folder 454)
      - 504. Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA) - Negro opportunities, 1966 September 6 (Box 12, Folder 455)
      - 505. G. Douglas Pugh appointment, 1966 September 19 (Box 12, Folder 456)
      - 506. Noncommercial television, 1966 October 4 (Box 12, Folder 457)
      - 507. F. Champion Ward appointment, 1966 October 2 (Box 12, Folder 458)
      - 508. Resources and Environment Program - Corkscrew Swamp Sanctuary, 1966 October 10 (Box 12, Folder 459)
      - 509. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - American Federation of the Arts films, 1966 October 13 (Box 12, Folder 460)
      - 510. Urban Extension, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 461)
        File also contains a copy of an October 16, 1968 press release along with that release's supplementary document. These items are located in Series 1, Subseries 2, File 633. Federal Communications Commission (FCC) submission (Folder 593) and Series 1, Subseries 2, Comments of the Ford Foundation in the Matter of Free or Reduced Rate Interconnection Service for Noncommercial Educational Broadcasting (Folder 594). They were likely misfiled prior to the collection's ingestion by the RAC.
      - 511. Planed Parenthood Federation of America, 1966 October-December (Box 12, Folder 462)
        File also contains a copy of a December 12, 1966 press release located in Series 1, Subseries 2, File: 518. Special Projects in Education (SPE) – Satellite (Folder 470). The item was likely misfiled prior to the collection's ingestion by the RAC.
      - 511a. Columbia Special Program grant, 1966 October 31 (Box 12, Folder 463)
      - 512. International Affairs Program (IA) and Overseas Development Program (OD) - University development, 1966 November 2 (Box 12, Folder 464)
      - 513. Engineering residencies, 1966 November 3 (Box 12, Folder 465)
      - 514. Frank Bowles appointment, 1966 November 7 (Box 12, Folder 466)
      - 515. Technology in education, 1966 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 467)
      - 516. Public Affairs Program (PA) - National Office for the Rights of the Indigent (NORI), 1966 November 22 (Box 12, Folder 468)
      - 517. Minority affairs - Negro businesses, 1966 December 8 (Box 12, Folder 469)
      - 518. Special Projects in Education (SPE) - Satellite, 1966 December 12 (Box 12, Folder 470)
      - 519. Education Division (ED) - Barnard and Teachers Colleges, 1966 December 14 (Box 12, Folder 471)
      - 520. Public Affairs Program (PA) - Crime and administration of justice, 1966 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 472)
      - 520a. Alternate lead for No. 520, 1966 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 473)
      - 521. Alexander Heard appointment to Ford Foundation Board of Trustees, 1966 December 16 (Box 12, Folder 474)
      - 522. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) and National Urban League, 1967 January 3 (Box 12, Folder 475)
      - 523. International Training and Research Program (ITR) - International Bilingual Center, 1967 January 17 (Box 12, Folder 476)
      - 524. WCET channel, 1967 January 23 (Box 12, Folder 477)
      - 525. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA), 1967 January 31 (Box 12, Folder 478)
      - 526. International Affairs Program (IA), 1967 February 8 (Box 12, Folder 479)
      - 526a. Alternate lead for No. 526, 1967 February 8 (Box 12, Folder 480)
      - 527. The Carnegie Corporation and The Fund for the Advancement of Education (TFAE), 1967 February 12 (Box 12, Folder 481)
      - 528. Public Affairs Program (PA), 1967 February 14 (Box 12, Folder 482)
      - 529. National Affairs and International Divisions, 1967 February 21 (Box 12, Folder 483)
      - 530. President Lyndon B. Johnson and educational television (ETV), 1967 February 28 (Box 12, Folder 484)
      - 531. Population, 1967 March 16 (Box 12, Folder 485)
      - 532. Annual Report, 1967 March 19 (Box 13, Folder 486)
      - 533. Overseas Development Program (OD) - Agriculture, 1967 March 23 (Box 13, Folder 487)
      - 534. Submission to Federal Communication Commission (FCC), 1967 April 3 (Box 13, Folder 488)
      - 534a. Carnegie Corporation and Ford Foundation grants to Vassar College and Yale University, 1967 April 7 (Box 13, Folder 489)
      - 535. Doctoral education, 1967 April 9 (Box 13, Folder 490)
      - 536. National Affairs Division, Office of Social Development (SD) - Zion Non-Profit Charitable Trust of Philadelphia, 1967 April 14 (Box 13, Folder 491)
      - 537. National Affairs Division, Office of Social Development (SD) - Minority groups, 1967 April 20 (Box 13, Folder 492)
      - 538. Ford Foundation President McGeorge Bundy statement, 1967 April 19 (Box 13, Folder 493)
      - 539. Scholarly exchange program between Poland and the West, 1967 April 28 (Box 13, Folder 494)
      - 540. The Fund for the Advancement of Education (TFAE), 1967 April 30 (Box 13, Folder 495)
      - 541. National Affairs Division, Government and Law Program (GL), 1967 May 3 (Box 13, Folder 496)
      - 542. Carnegie Corporation and Ford Foundation - National Governors' Conference, 1967 May 5 (Box 13, Folder 497)
      - 543. National Affairs Division - Civil rights and leadership, 1967 May 12 (Box 13, Folder 498)
      - 544. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Negro theater, 1967 May 15 (Box 13, Folder 499)
      - 545. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Theater, 1967 May 19 (Box 13, Folder 500)
      - 545a. Attachment to No. 545, 1967 May 19 (Box 13, Folder 501)
      - 546. National Affairs Division, Office of Social Development (SD) - Civil rights, 1967 May 23 (Box 13, Folder 502)
      - 547. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - Daedelus journal, 1967 June 1 (Box 13, Folder 503)
      - 548. Asian studies, 1967 June 6 (Box 13, Folder 504)
      - 549. Kermit Gordon appointment to Ford Foundation Board of Trustees, 1967 June 5 (Box 13, Folder 505)
      - 550. James W. Bryant appointment, 1967 June 6 (Box 13, Folder 506)
      - 551. Cooperative education, 1967 June 22 (Box 13, Folder 507)
      - 552. National Affairs Division, Government and Law Program (GL) - Government planning-programming-budgeting, 1967 June 29 (Box 13, Folder 508)
      - 553. Business administration and economic fellowships, 1967 June 30 (Box 13, Folder 509)
      - 554. Howard R. Dressner appointment, 1967 July 5 (Box 13, Folder 510)
      - 555. Experimental school units, 1967 July 6 (Box 13, Folder 511)
      - 556. Education and Research, Special Projects - Negro higher education, 1967 July 7 (Box 13, Folder 512)
      - 557. National Affairs Division, Office for Social Development (SD) - Cleveland grants, 1967 July 14 (Box 13, Folder 513)
      - 558. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA) - APA-Phoenix, 1967 July 20 (Box 13, Folder 514)
      - 559. J. Wayne Fredericks appointment, 1967 July 23 (Box 13, Folder 515)
      - 560. Humanities and the Arts Program (HA), 1967 July 25 (Box 13, Folder 516)